[{"answer": "What, you know what, the keys. I want the keys. You've lost your key privileges", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Keys.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "No, come on", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "What, what, I thought you went to the movies", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Keys.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Now how was I supposed to know it was going to be sold out", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Now how was I supposed to know it was going to be sold out", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Keys.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "What point", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "What point", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Keys.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Just give me another chance", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "It's not going to happen again", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Keys.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "O.K., fine, go ahead, you take the keys! But you're going to regret this.  New scene. my friend's apartment, the next day. my friend is now giving his spare keys to my friend", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Oh, I'm not, uh..", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Keys.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "my friend, give him the keys back", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Do you ever yearn", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Keys.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I yearn", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Yearn? Do I yearn", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Keys.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "You yearn", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "You yearn", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Keys.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Well, not recently. I craved. I crave all the time, constant craving...but I haven't yearned", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Aw, my friend, don't start..", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Keys.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I am not! What you call wasting, I call living! I'm living my life", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Why", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Keys.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Yeah, I think I got a touch of something, too", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Anyway, so he gave me his spare keys, now he wants to have my keys, so I need mine back from you", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Keys.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I don't know. He said he wants to be my", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Don't play coy with me, my friend, I'm not in the mood", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Keys.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Is he being coy", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "What...", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Keys.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Nothing. I didn't say anything", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Nothing. I didn't say anything", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Keys.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Yeah, I saw it. I saw it! I did, I saw it. Yep", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Yeah, I saw it. I saw it! I did, I saw it. Yep", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Keys.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "I didn't say anything", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "my friend! Way to come through with the keys! Sit down, I'm buying you dinner", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Keys.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Don't feel right? What are you talking about", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Just because you have someone's spare keys, it doesn't entitle you to break into their apartment. That's the reason you took away my friend's keys", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Keys.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Yes, well, if you had never taken your keys back from my friend, he never would have taken his back from you and given 'em to me, in which case I wouldn't have had to take mine back from her", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "my friend, give them to me, I want these keys.  I don't want to get physical", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Keys.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Do you wanna fight", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Yes! And then the handsome young prince was cast out into the cruel, cruel world", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Keys.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Oh, he's cold", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "They were in here, I saw her put 'em in here", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Keys.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Well, what do they look like", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Well, this is great", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Keys.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "They look like keys, my friend. They look exactly like keys. ", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "They look like keys, my friend. They look exactly like keys. ", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Keys.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Well, they've gotta be here somewhere", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "He forced me to", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Keys.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Yes you did", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "And I don't want you to hold mine", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Keys.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "Good! Don't! Are these my keys", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "Good! I won't", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Keys.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "These aren't my keys", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "O.K., can I just watch the show?  God, what an asshole", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Keys.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "I didn't say anything", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "I didn't say anything", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Keys.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "my friend's on", "qsentId": 56}]